{
    "subject": "resource/Fablehaven:_Rise_of_the_Evening_Star",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star is a fantasy novel written by Brandon Mull. The book was released on May 31, 2007. It is the second book in the Fablehaven series. Its sequel is Fablehaven: Grip of the Shadow Plague.",
    "human_readable": "Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star is a fantasy novel written by Brandon Mull.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9548143148422241,
            "question": "Who wrote Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8060420155525208,
            "question": "Is Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star a work of fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7576151490211487,
            "question": "What genre is Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7060859799385071,
            "question": "What might a reader expect to find in Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041974186897278,
            "question": "Can you name another book by Brandon Mull?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4444039463996887,
            "question": "What is the title of the fantasy novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23899473249912262,
            "question": "What makes a good fantasy novel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23833312094211578,
            "question": "What is a common theme found in fantasy novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17850221693515778,
            "question": "Do you enjoy reading fantasy novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15478183329105377,
            "question": "What kind of stories are typically found in the fantasy genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star is a fantasy novel written by Brandon Mull.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8265_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you enjoy reading fantasy novels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8265_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a common theme found in fantasy novels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8265_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a good fantasy novel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8265_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8265_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Fablehaven: Rise of the Evening Star is a fantasy novel written by Brandon Mull.\" The context clearly mentions it as such in multiple documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}